从俄罗斯来的3万美元。
30,000 from the Russians
不，来自法国。
no from the French
我们每天都捕获比这更多的俄罗斯人。
from the Russians we capture more than that every day
邮递员在哪？
where's the postman
战争是战争，糖果是糖果。
war is war and snaps is snaps
这必须继续。
the business must go on
你今天早上还没发邮件吗？
you didn't leave the mail yet this morning
对不起，梅耶先生。
ah I'm sorry Mister Meyer
你好，彼得。
hello himostos
今天有什么给我们的吗？没有。
anything for us today no
没问题，小伙子。
no Master Pete
这里有什么吗？
well there must be something here
你的小混混，哈哈。
here is your young rascal hahaha
这是最后一封我要送的信。
there this is the last mail I deliver anyhow
明天我换上新制服。
what tomorrow I change uniform
你要入伍了，是的。
you're going in the army yes
我被召集，我是预备役的上尉。
I was called I'm a sergeant in the reserves
你知道吗？
you know
如果几个月后还没结束，我会自告奋勇的。
I'll be called myself if it doesn't end in a few months
会的。
uh it will though
我相信你是对的，梅耶先生。
I'm sure you're right Mister Meyer
加入了军队，为了击败敌人。
we're joined the mighty army to defeat the enemy
我们的国家，我们的父亲。
our country our father
你可能会爱上这份工作。
now my beloved friends
这就是我们必须做的，用全部力量发动攻击。
this is what we must do strike with all our power
竭尽全力。
give every ounce of strength
在年底之前赢得胜利。
to win victory before the end of the year
我很不情愿地提及这个问题。
it is with reluctance that I bring this subject up
好的
again
你们是祖国的生力军。
you are the life of the fatherland
你们这些男孩，你们是德国的铁人。
you boys you are the iron men of Germany
你是我们的英雄，将击退敌人。
you are the gay heroes who will repulse the enemy
当你被召唤时。
when you are called upon to do so
我不应该建议。
it is not for me to suggest
你们中的任何人都应该站起来。
that any of you should stand up
并愿意为国而战。
and offer to defend his country
然而，
but
我想知道是否有这样的想法在你们的脑海中。
I wonder if such a thing is going through your heads
我知道在一所学校里，
I know that in one of the schools the
在教室里，男孩们站了起来。
boys have risen up in the classroom
并在混乱中列出了。
and enlisted in a mass
当然，如果这里也发生这样的事情。
and of course if such a thing should happen here
你不会责怪我有一点自豪感。
you would not blame me for a feeling of pride
也许
perhaps
有些人会说你还不应该去。
some will say that you should not be allowed to go yet
你太年轻，有家，有母亲。
that you are too young that you have homes mothers
父亲，你们不应该被分离。
fathers that you should not be torn away
你们的父亲忘了自己的故土吗？
are your fathers so forgetful of their fatherland
他们宁愿让它灭亡，也不愿让你。
that they would let it perish rather than you
你的母亲如此脆弱。
are your mothers so weak
他们不能让儿子去捍卫土地。
that they cannot send a son to defend the land
这是他们的诞生之地，毕竟。
which gave them birth and after all
对于一个男孩来说，一点点经历是否真的如此糟糕？
is a little experience such a bad thing for a boy
穿着制服的荣耀是什么？
is the honor of wearing a uniform
我们应该从什么地方逃跑？
something from which we should run
如果我们的年轻女士们为那些穿着它的人感到骄傲，那该怎么办？
and if our young ladies glory in those who wear it
这有什么值得羞耻的吗？
is that anything to be ashamed of
我知道你从未渴望过英雄的赞美。
I know you have never desired the adulation of heroes
这不是我的教学内容。
that has not been part of my teaching
我们努力使自己有价值。
we have sought to make ourselves worthy
并让声誉随之而来。
and let a claim come when it would
但在战场上最出色是一种美德。
but to be foremost in battle is a virtue
不值得轻视，我相信这将是一场快速的战争。
not to be despised I believe it will be a quick war
但会有很少的损失。
but there will be few losses
但如果有损失，就必须有。
but if losses there must be
让我们记住那句拉丁语。
then let us remember the Latin phrase
这句必曾在许多罗马人的嘴边。
which must have come to the lips of many a Roman
当他在异国战场上站立时。
when he stood in battle in a foreign land
为国捐躯，甘之如饴。
Dulce et decorum est pro patria Mori
甘甜而合适，为了父land而死。
sweet and fitting it is to die for the fatherland
你们中有些人可能有野心。
some of you may have ambitions
我认识一个年轻人。
I know of one young man
谁作为作家有着巨大的潜力。
who has great promise as a writer
他写了一部悲剧的第一幕。
and he has written the first act of a tragedy
这将是对大师们的一种荣誉。
which would be a credit to one of the masters
他在梦里，我猜。
and he is dreaming I suppose
追随戈特和希拉的足迹。
of following in the footsteps of Goethe and Schiller
我希望他会，但现在国家需要我们。
and I hope he will but now our country calls
国家需要领导者。
the fatherland needs leaders
个人野心必须抛弃。
personal ambition must be thrown aside
为了我们国家的伟大牺牲。
in the one great sacrifice for our country
这是你们生活的辉煌开始。
here is a glorious beginning for your lives
荣耀之地呼唤你。
the field of honor calls you
我们为什么在这里？
why are we here
你去掉了你的拦路虎。
you crop what has kept you back
你的母亲知道你有多需要。
you mother you know how much you are needed
啊，我看你看向你的领袖，我也看向你。
ah I see you look at your leader and I too look to you
保罗·鲍默
Paul Bowman
我想知道你会做什么。
and I wonder what you are going to do
我去，我想去。
I'll go I wanna go
我也会去。
count on me me too
我准备好了，我不会待在家里。
I'm ready I'm not gonna stay home
结束了，不再有课。
it is now no more classes
没人想和你在一起。
no more classes no more classes
别放弃，来吧，BAME。
don't be a quitter come on BAME
紧紧团结，这是我们必须做的。
stick together that's what we've got to do
让我们都团结在一起。
let's all stick together
我们会通过贝尔来打电话给她。
we'll be generous to call her through BAME
好的好的。
alright alright
我走了。
I'll go that's the way
去吧。
let's go
嗨，我来了。
Sri Sri Sarkar
哦，是的，你说得对。
oh and they are they are
躺在那里的士兵们，哈哈。
even lying there soldiers hahaha
你说什么，将军？哈哈。
anything you say general hahaha
注意。
detail
拦住她，把她带走。
hold left hand
穿上制服，准备报告，拉紧。
get in the uniforms ready to report pull on
我猜你的地方就像这样。
I bet your place like this
要保持良好状态，为长途行军做好准备。
gets in good condition it has to be for the long march
我要去骑骑骑马。
or I'm gonna get the cavalry and ride
我不会骑骑兵。
you know no cavalry for me
步兵是你看到战斗的地方。
infantry is where you see the fighting
我想知道所有的枪都在哪？
where are all the guns that's what I wanna know
你还得等很久才能得到枪。
well you don't get a gun for a long while yet
如果我要击败敌人，
well if I'm gonna bump off the enemy
我得多练习一下。啊。
I gotta have some practice ow
我要的是贝纳特的训练，就是这样。
bandit drill that's what I want
啊。
ah
那次你想要奖牌吗，妈妈？
you want a medal that time mother
等一个月，我就会被他们覆盖。
you wait about a month I'll be covered with them
别让你的靴子对着我。
say keep your boots out of my face
为什么要把那些靴子放在你的脸上呢？
why it's an honor to have those boots in your face
他们是军队中最好的一双。
they're the best pair in the army
我叔叔给了我，看这一双。
my uncle gave them to me just look at that
特殊进口皮革
special imported leather
放到你喜欢的任何地方，但不要放在我面前。
put them any place you like except in my face
即使是厨房女佣也不看我在这个任务中。
not even a kitchen maid look at me in this mission
好吧，为了爱。
well for the love of
这就是彼得斯顿，没错。
it's himmelstoss so it is
全副武装，嗨，希米。
and all dressed up hello himmy
你没想到这么快就会再见我吧？
you didn't think you'd see me again so soon did you
你看到我的军衔了吗？
you see my rank sure
好的，那就这样。
all right then
我们当然很高兴见到你，希莫斯。
give us toast we certainly are glad to see you
你说我要说什么？
what did you say I was going to say
别提了，你怎么了，海默斯·托斯？
never mind what's the matter with you himostos
当你对上司说话时，
when you address your superior officer
说“先生”。
say sir
他从哪里得到这件漂亮的制服？
where did he get this nice uniform
你有没有邮件？
have you been in the mail
让他别乱说话。
force himy quiet
亲爱的，你在大喊。
my dear fellow you're shouting
来吧，艾默斯科。
ah come on himostos
现在等一下，把假胡子摘下来。
we know you take off the false whiskers
我相信你是认真的，你会发现我也是认真的。
I believe you mean it you'll find out that I mean it
三天前你还在邮局，现在就安静下来。
well only three days ago you were our postman shut up
来吧。
come here
请注意。
line up
让他们排队，我们来好好想一想。
get in some kind of a line that we can count on
他们都在那边。 他们都在那边。
all of them line up on the side
那真是一幅美丽的景象。
what a pretty sight that is
你是否听说过排队？
have you never heard of standing in line
你会搞得一团糟。
you'll make a fine mess of it
嗯，我得教教你。
well I'll have to teach you
我们全天都要花在这上面，对吧？
we'll spend the whole day on it huh
你可能是个笨蛋，但我已经习惯了。
you may be stupid but I'm used to that
然后还有很多其他事情。
and then there'll be plenty of other things too
哦，我不会忽视你。
oh I'll not neglect you
嗯
hmm
你本来就不值什么，但我会尽力。
you're not much to begin with but I'll do my best
我明白了。
I see that
我们带着一点误解来了。
we have come here with a slight misunderstanding
我们也会纠正这个错误。
and we'll correct that too
我们会的，是吧？
won't we huh
第一件要做的事就是忘记。
and the first thing to do is to forget
你所知道的一切，你所学过的一切。
everything you ever knew everything you ever Learned
忘记看。
forget see
忘掉你的身份。
forget what you've been
你认为你会成为什么？
and what you think you're going to be
根据他们的说法，
you're going to be soldiers
这就是全部。
and that's all
我要从你身上取出母亲的乳汁。
I'll take the mother's milk out of you
我不会让你变得坚硬。
I'll make you hard boiled
我要把你们训练成士兵，否则就杀了你们。
I'll make soldiers out of you or kill you
现在
now
闭嘴。
shut up
嘿
OK
匹配
match
脱离
detachment
去吧，去。
lie down go
头低。
head down
头低一点，巴玛。
keep your head down bummer
分遣队
detachment
站起来。
get up
哦糟了。
I'll sink
你叫那叫歌吗？他们来了，快点。
do you call that singing detachment come
所以我们没有精神，是吗？
so we have no spirit huh
我们不想休息。
we are in no mood for recreation
我们想要的是工作，好的，那么我们就回去工作吧。
work is what we want good then we'll go back to work
不，不让我去
no sink on the dog
下一页
on the dog
让他来。
laten voor
强壮的臂膀和胸膛。
hände Raus ihr Strumpferfrauen
把手伸出来，你的腿。
hände Raus ihr Strumpferfrauen Fernhalt
下达命令。
order an
三点检查。
inspection at 3
那就是说，我们没有休息时间。
that's fine it means we get no time off
为了检查，我们需要四小时准备。
we take four hours to get ready for inspection
我想知道他在想什么。
I'd like to know what's in his mind
是的，你得到了。
he hasn't got it well
我有一天会把他剖开看看。
I'm gonna cut him open sometime and find out
他的皮肤太厚，不会被刺伤。
too thick skinned he won't cut
这是他让我失望的第四次。
this is the fourth time he's made me disappoint
那个可怜的女孩。
that poor girl
好的，让我看看。
arm right
哦
arm
左肩上
left shoulder arm
跑。
right squad
右侧的颜色
right cover
好 好 好 好 好 好 好 好 好 好 好
right back left left
是的
Left Left Left
好。
跑
Left Left Left
啊
Left Left Right
两三
Left
对，是的。
Right Left
嗯嗯
Left Left left
5 6
7 8
和打。
9 10 11 12 13
下一页。
14 15
谢谢你。
16 17 18 19
好的，哦。
20 21 22
下一页
23 24 25 26
哎呀
27 28
他必须走。
29 30
很好的工作，明天他们将上前线。
excellent work they're going up front tomorrow
我建议晚些时候离去。
I recommend leave till midnight
非常好，先生。
very good sir
let's go let's go
我来了。
let's go let's go let's go
只剩下一个。
1 left
对的。
right about
你抓到了，躺下。
you touch man lie down
前进。
roll forward
他毁了我们的假期，我永远不会原谅他。
he spoiled our leave I'll never forgive him for that
老鼠要到午夜离开。
the rat leave till midnight
到午夜才能晾干我们的衣服。
it'll take till midnight to dry our clothes
现在去找那只臭猴子吧。
there goes the filthy ape now
我们在这泥巴上苦苦挣扎。
while we slave over this MUD
他去喝几杯。
he goes off to have a few drinks
有一天，我要狠狠地打他一巴掌。
someday I'm going to take one smack at him
一个我也。
just one me too
从现在起，这将是我的终身工作。
that's gonna be my life's work from now on
为什么只有一个？我
why only one I'm
我要打几下，甚至可能在他低头的时候踢他一脚。
gonna take several I might even kick him when he's down
我觉得我自己。
I feel mean
你在做什么？
what are you doing
你不打算吃零食吗？什么？
you're not gonna desert are you what
听着，我有个想法。
listen I've got an idea
向前滚，躺下。
roll forward lie down
躺下
lights out
滚过去。
roll forward
hey hey
嘿嘿嘿。
hey hey hey
嘿嘿嘿
停下。
stop
停下！
it stop it
来吧。
我有个想法，你听听。
2 3 4 5
6 个小时
6 7 8
来吧，宝贝。
come on babe
来吧，你这个笨蛋。
come on you fool babe
起来。
get up
来吧。
come on
这里有一些新的，刚从萝卜地里摘来的。
here's some more fresh from the turnip patch
我猜这就是我们碰到的地方。
I suppose this is where we bump
我是Vesta。
that's me I'm Vesta
这就是他住的地方。
and this is where he lives
我不知道。
I didn't know well
你现在知道了。
you know now
是的，当然。
yes yes of course
好的。
sorry
有一个篮球。
there's a basketball
我们什么时候吃过呢？
hey when did we eat last
别提醒我，直到你说话我还挺好的。
don't remind me I was fine until you spoke
我们现在在哪里？我不知道。
where are we anyway I don't know
铁路站的名字被关闭了。
the name on the railroad station's been shut off
一定有什么可吃的地方。
there must be something to eat somewhere
我告诉你我会做什么，我会问那帮人。
I'll tell you what I'll do I'll ask those fellows
对不起打扰你。
sorry to disturb you
西顿先生，哦。
Mister Weston oh
认识达特林，他是最好的农夫。
meet datering the better farmer never lived
先生查登，请坐下。
and Mister Chadwick sit down
你看，我们从早餐以来就没吃过东西。
you see we haven't eaten since breakfast
我们开始了
and we thought
你能告诉我们该怎么办吗？
maybe you could tell us what we ought to do about it
立即吃东西。
eat without further delay
那有什么好笑的？
what's funny about that
这是一个不适合带食欲的地方，士兵。
it's a bad town to bring an appetite to soldier
我们自昨天早上就在这里。
we've been here since yesterday morning
我们一直生活在草垛和剃刀上。
and we've been living on bail hay and razor blades
愿意买我们的食物。
we're willing to buy our food
哪里有食堂？哈哈。
where's the canteen ha ha
哈哈
ha ha
这一带唯一的食堂已关门。
the only canteen in these regions is out
寻找补给，听说过卡奇尼斯基吗？
looking for supplies ever hear of Kaczynski
谁是卡切尼斯基？
who Kaczynski
他很神奇，在25英里范围内没有食物。
he's uncanny there's any food within 25 miles
他会去拿的。
he'll be the one to get it
嘿，糟了。
hey fuck
这是一个简化中文翻译：
hop
嗯？
我不知道我在做什么。
I don't know why I'm doing this
哈哈。
hahaha
这是什么？未来总参谋部的志愿者？
what is this volunteers for the future General Staff
有一天，我要把你们这些志願者拆散。
sometime I'm gonna take one of you volunteers apart
查明。
and find out
为什么你离开学校加入了军队？
what makes you leave school and join the army
这是一个游乐场。
it is this is a playground
饿了，是的。
hungry yes sir
等一下。
hey wait a minute
等待一封邀请函。
wait a minute that's no invitation
你能付钱吗？
can you pay yes
当然。
sure
我有钱吗？没有。
I have money no
不是钱，只是一张纸。
not money that's just piece of paper
你有烟吗？
and you got any cigarettes
雪茄、肥皂、香槟。
cigars or soap cognac
你疯了吗？这里的东西不够我们用。
are you crazy there ain't enough here for us
我希望你们三个人会被打掉。
I wish you 3 would get bumped off
我厌倦了无谓地给你喂食。
I'm tired of feeding you for nothing
带上你所有的东西。
bring everything you've got
哈嗯。
cap hmm
你今晚的电线细节在哪？
you got the wiring detail tonight where
和这帮人一起过墓地。
past the graveyard with this bunch
今晚很安静，你可以教他几点。
it's quiet tonight you can teach him a couple of things
谢谢，我宁愿独自完成。
thanks I'd rather do it alone
这些娃娃被杀得太快了。
these babes get killed off too fast
警方在等着。
well the law is waiting
昨晚我饿得睡不着。
last night I was too hungry to sleep
当我把皱纹从肚子里取出来时，晚上。
and tonight when I get the wrinkles out of my gut
他们想到了电线任务。
they think up wiring duty
好吧，轮到你了。
well here's your chance
为国而战的英雄。
heroes for the fatherland
快点，拿你的东西，我们走吧。
come on get your stuff let's get out of here
你能开车吗？
is there any way to drive
让他开车怎么开都行。
let him drive anyway he wants
假设他断了你的手臂。
suppose he breaks your arm
你会被送回家的。
you get sent home don't you
好得多，比起你的肠子被夹住要好。
a lot better than having a hold in your guts
如果你们中还有人。
if there's any of you left
我早上会来接你。
I'll pick you up in the morning
那你给我们的车程没把我们都打死。
well if that ride you gave us didn't kill us
不会发生什么，准时到达。
nothing will and be on time
我不想错过早餐。
I don't want to miss my breakfast
等一下，等你的军队，爸爸。
huh you better wait for your army papa
这里，这里。
here here
别那么保守。
don't be so backward
孩子们，听我说。
listen children
我们只需轻轻晃动一根线。
all we gotta do is to swing a little wire
我们在垃圾堆里捡起来。
we pick it up at the dump
并将其运送到我们需要的地方。
and carry it to where we need it
现在你要看到一些炮火。
now you're gonna see some shellfire
你会害怕的，看。
and you're gonna be scared see
好的，小伙子，起来。
it's all right boy get up
嗯，没关系。
yeah never mind
这也发生在比你更优秀的人身上。
it's happened to better men than you
这也发生在我身上。
and it's happened to me
当我们回来时
when we come back
我会给你们每个人买一些干净的内裤。
I'll get you all some nice clean underwear
那是一種顯示。
that kind of shell
你不需要多注意。
you don't have to pay much attention to
那些大家伙们吵得很厉害。
those big fellas just make a lot of noise
落在前线后约五英里处。
and land about 5 miles behind the line
我们要注意的事情。
the things we've got to watch out for
就像那些，他们很少提前警告。
are the light ones they don't give you much warning
他们走了。
they go
当你听到“去”的时候，就走。
and when you hear that go
母亲之美
Mother Nature
洗涤自己，不要靠近火。
freshen yourselves down a fire
沉浸在其中。
bury yourselves deep in the water
只需盯着我看。
just keep your eyes on me
当你看到我翻身时，你也翻身。
when you see me flop you flop
只需试图在我之前完成。
only try to beat me to it
请注意。
listen
我来给你示范。
I'll show you how it's done
给我几个。
give me a couple of those
为了消灭噪音，让我们去。
it's to kill the noise John
你看到了吗？
you see that
那是什么意思，我被困扰了？
what that mean I'm bothered
我被困了，我什么都看不见。
I'm blind I can't see anything
我的眼睛，我看不见。
my eyes I can't see
哦我的天啊。
oh my God
是的，亲爱的。
it's babe
它是宝贝，宝贝。
it's babe babe
我去拿你的。
I'll go get you I'll go get
你好。
you
他死了。
he's dead
他死了，你为什么冒着生命危险把他带进来？
he's dead why did you risk your life bringing him in
但这是贝比。
but it's pain
我的朋友，不管是谁，这都是个遗体。
my friend it's a corpse no matter who it is
我不希望你们再这样做。
I don't any of you ever do that again
把他放在那边。
put him over there
我爱你，我爱你。
mind the wire mind the wire
注意电线。
mind the wire
我去找你。 我去找你。
再见。
Hasta LA
我知道。
hasta LA
五次。
alright come on
拿你的包，快点。
get your packs and pull in hurry up
快点，赶快。
come on hurry up
好的。
come on
拿你的包，快点跟进。
get your packs and pull in
帕特，我们在做什么？
Pat what are we doing
发生了什么？你会对他们所有人感到厌恶。
what's happening you'll hate them all to the march
但我们是为了另一个派对。
well we're too for the love of another party
这一次会持续很久。
and this one is gonna last a long time
来吧。
come on
出发吧。
here we go
注意，注意！
Germany attention
哈拉 我
General hands
什么是正确的，什么是错误的？
what's right March
别碰那位女王，她是我的。
take your hands off that queen takes it
你认为那是女王吗？
well if you think that's a queen
再看，那是个杰克。
look again that's a Jack
是的，坦白说。
yeah honestly
这些车都一样看。哈哈。
these cards all look alike ha ha
太吵了，我无法玩。
that's too noisy I can't play
我猜你的脆弱神经承受不了。
I suppose your delicate nerves can't stand it
这是奥斯卡，他的儿子。
that's Oscar the son of a
看那。
look at that
别那么高傲，你可能会后悔没有这个。
don't be so snooty you may wish you had this back
再过两天就这样了。
about 2 more days of this
被老鼠咬过的面包末端会尝起来。
rat bitten end of a piece of bread's gonna taste
就像一块水果蛋糕。
just like a hunk of fruitcake
不会，不会再坚持两天。
it wouldn't it wouldn't last two more days
我告诉你这会是个糟糕的吗？
would it did I tell you this was gonna be a bad one
我对白天没那么在意。
I don't mind the days so much
它整晚都在扰乱我们。
it's keeping up all night
再过两天就是一周，小伙子。
two more days makes a week kid
那么你就可以说你经历过火场。
then you can say you've been under fire
你不怕吗？
you're not scared are you
不，我只是问问而已。
no I was just asking that's all
想再玩一会儿吗？
Wanna play some more do you
当然。
sure
好的，我明白了。
alright my dear
赶紧把你的靴子拿回来，不然奥斯卡会吃掉的。
you better get your boot back before Oscar eats that
哈哈哈
ha ha ha ha ha
孩子没问题。
the kids alright
嗯。
same
哦，天啊。
oh God
你看不出来是他吗？
can't you see his fame
他不想来打仗。
he didn't want to come to war
不。
no
不是的，这不是鲍恩。
no it isn't Bane
这不就是他吗？
it isn't Bane
这是加莫拉。
it's Gamora
我是他，闭嘴，威廉。
it's me shut up William
这里已经很糟了。
it's bad enough in here as it is
所有的
every
一切都好，弗朗兹。
everything's all right Franz
你在梦里。
you're dreaming
我觉得你只是在梦里。
I think something you're just dreaming I guess
埃德迪的攻击。
attack hunt Eddie's
情况越来越糟。
the rise is getting worse
两艘潜艇和两座掩体消失了。
men and 2 more dugouts gone
好的，我明白了。
however
我们会尽力在傍晚前把食物送到这里。
we'll do our best to get some food up here by evening
你干嘛这么做？闭嘴。
what did you do that for shut up
抓住他。
grab him
不，现在停下。
no now hold
你现在好吗？
you alright now
我觉得是的。
I think so
不能坚持多长时间了。
couldn't hold out much longer
我的天，这糟透了。
oh my God it's probably terrible
不，别。
no don't
他的肚子被打了。
he's been hit in the stomach
没什么可喝的，去拿个雪茄。
he didn't have anything to drink get a stretcher
你在哪儿，卡米克？
where did it get you Camrick
这是，先生，拿他的头。
here it is sir take his head
好的，把他抬出去。
alright take him out
真的吗，先生？
you serious sir
我不确定。
I'm not sure
告诉其他人，他没事。
tell the others he's alright
是的，先生。
yes sir
我们要打仗，为什么不打？
we're going to fight why don't we fight
我们为什么不过去？
why don't we go over
在这里呆下去会让你发疯。
go crazy staying here
让我们做点什么。
let's do something
让我们去追他。坐下。
let's go after him sit down
库克·阿尔斯有胆子吗？
if Cook Alice had any guts
他试图带些东西过去。
he'd try to bring something through
他远在后方。
he's so far behind the lines
他听不到枪声。
he can't hear the shooting
猫有什么吗？
here's cat got anything
有没有运气？我们需要分摊这件事。
any luck we'll have to split this up among us
我们也需要水。
we need water too
是的，还有要说的。
yes and dessert
还有羽绒床睡。
and a feather bed to sleep on
跑。
right right right
对，对。
right right
对对对
right right right right
那是什么？
what's that
嘿
hey
come on come on
啊
好的，我来帮你。
come on come on
快点，快点。
来了。
come on come on come
再来一次。
on come on
快点。
come on come on come on
哦，我的天啊！
oh my God
哦，我的天啊。
哦 耶！
oh my God oh
哦 哦
my God
你不能一直保持这个姿势，伙计。
you can't hold this position man
回到你的队伍。
back to your own line
我在左边，我在跑步。
I'm left I'm jogging
快出去。
get out of there
我想再看一次。
Ich will auf einmal wieder sehen
乐高乐高乐高
Lego Lego Lego
小人小人
Lego Lego
快填满，我还有其他事要做。
fill it up and hurry up I've got other things to do
我已经等了三个星期。
I've been waiting for this for three weeks
当他们都来时。
when they all get here
你想要什么？
what do you want
喂饱你那看起来像家伙的儿子。
feed your homie looking son of a frog's leg
你觉得我想要什么？
what do you think I want
安静，等你们都来了再给你们吃。
shut up I'll feed you when you're all here
我们现在都在，只剩下一半公司。
we're all here now only half the company's here
唤醒剩下的人。
get the rest wake'em up
哈哈。
ha ha ha
是的，我希望能唤醒他。
yeah I wish I could wake'em up
剩下的是80人。
there's 80 of us left
剩下的人在收容站或在花坛里。
the rest is in dressing stations or pushing up daisies
八十，我为一百五十人做饭。
eighty and I cook for 150
好的，我们有足够的。
alright we'll have enough for one
快点，休息一下。
come on this off
你是说你会为150人煮豆子吗？
you mean you cook beans for 150
你有150块的面包和150块的火腿。
and you've got bread for 150 and sausage for 150
为了150的一切，我要倒退。
and tobacco for 150 everything
这一切都不对，我应该被通知。
it's all wrong I should have been notified
什么丰盛的餐桌，每个人都能享受。
what a feast everyone gets
两个问题。
two issues
想象一下，想象一下。
get back in line get back in line
哦不。
oh no
那是一个多。
that's one too
我不能给80人分配150人份的食物。
I can't give 80 men what's meant for 150
听着。
listen
你为第二公司提供了配方。
you drew rations for the 2nd company
你真的是？
didn't you
是的
yes
好的，我们是第二家公司。
all right we're the second company
我有我的任务，没错。
I've got my orders that's right
我们是第二家公司。
we're the second company
如果只有一半人回来了。
and if only half of us get back
这是我们的好运，快点。
that's our good luck come on
分发食物，快点。
dish it out come on
不，去吧。
no come on
哦，嘿。
come on oh hey
来吧。 来吧。 来吧。
hey come on
你是最胆小的那一个。
come on you're the yellowest back
从前，有一个名叫布恩的人，他曾开过一辆厨师车。
Boone that ever drew a cook wagon
你害怕的是剧本。
and you're scared of shells
我们只想从你那里听到一个小的“呜”声。
all we wanna hear out of you is one more little yip
我们会切你开，生吃你。
and we'll cut you up and eat you raw
你为什么把厨房放在这么远的地方？
why you keep your kitchen so far back in the lines
我们总是吃到的时候就已经冷了。
we never get anything to eat until it's cold
我们现在都在睡觉。
and we're asleep oh
你这下流的老鼠。
you low down rat
走开，否则我们会把这间酒吧搞得一团糟。
get out or we wreck the juke to hell back there
来吧，给我们点。
come on give us a
你好，请问有什么问题吗？
go
女士们
ladies
这里发生了什么？他为一百五十人做了饭。
what's going on here he's cooked for 150 sir
他只想给我们一半。
and he only wants to give us half
看起来不错，是的。
looks pretty good yes sir
给所有男性服务，他们可以使用。
serve the whole issue the men can use it
是的
yes sir
给我也来一个盘子。
and bring me a plate too yes
好的，就拿走吧。
alright take it all
拿所有的东西，给他们钱。
take everything give them honey
让他们得到他们想要的。
give them what they want
给它放，给它放。
fill it up fill it up
够了，够了。
别放，别放，有人在吗？
don't put that don't put that is anybody else in
这儿。
here
没关系，我就在这里。
don't mind me well
没关系，没必要提及。
that's alright don't mention it
你知道吧。
you know
我需要更多的豆子。
I could do with some more beans
去自助吧，那里还有更多。
go help yourself there's more over there
哦
oh
太远了。
it's too far
我想知道我们什么时候会回到前线。
I wonder when are we going back to the front
明天。
tomorrow
这足够让人失去食欲。
it's enough to take away a man's appetite
你知道他们明天又要把我们领进去吗？
you know if they're gonna march us in again tomorrow
我们要去看看卡梅拉怎么样。
we ought to go see how Kemrick is
那是个好主意。
that's a good idea I'll do that
伤员站离我们多远？
how far is the dressing station
大约两英里。
about 2 miles
我们可以送他的东西过去。
we could take his things to him
看起来很糟糕。
it seems rotten
想到这样的事情会发生给他。
to think of a thing like that happening to him
一个好人，像凯梅尔。
a nice fellow like Kemel ah
法国人
the French
他们确实应该受到惩罚，因为他们发动了这场战争。
certainly deserve to be punished for starting this war
大家都说不是他们。
everybody says it's somebody else
那么他们是如何开始战争的？
well how do they start a war
一个国家对另一个国家造成了伤害。
well one country offends another
一个国家如何冒犯另一个国家？
how could one country offend another
你是说德国有一座山吗？
you mean there's a mountain over in Germany
法国的一个田地惹恼了他。
gets mad at a field over in France
好吧，愚蠢。
well stupid
一个人冒犯另一个人。
one people offend another
哦，就是这样。
oh that's it
我根本不应该来这里，我也不觉得被冒犯。
I shouldn't be here at all I don't feel offended
对像你这样的流浪汉来说，这不适用。
it don't apply to tramps like you
好的，那我就可以立即回家了。
good then I can be going home right away ah
你试试看，你想被打吗？
you just try it you wanna get shot
开车的人是我。
the Kaiser and me
凯泽和我对这场战争的看法一样。
me and the Kaiser felt just alike about this war
我们都不想打仗。
we didn't either of us want any war
我要回家了。
so I'm going home
他已经在那了，肯定有人想要。
he's there already somebody must have wanted it
可能是英语。
maybe it was the English
不，我不愿射击任何英国人。
no I don't want to shoot any Englishman
我直到来这里才第一次看到。
I never saw one till I came up here
我想大多数人都没见过德国人。
and I suppose most of them never saw a German
直到他们来这里，没有。
till they came up here no
我确信他们没有被问过。
I'm sure they weren't asked about it no
嗯。
well
这一定对某人有好处。
it must be doing somebody some good
不是我和凯撒。
not me and the Kaiser
我觉得可能凯撒尔想要战争。
I think maybe the Kaiser wanted a war
你别把我们也算在内。
you leave us out of this
我不认为卡西亚斯已经得到了他需要的一切。
I don't see that the Kaiser's got everything he needs
嗯，我从没打过战争。
well he never had a war before
每个成年的皇帝都需要一棵树。
every full grown emperor needs one war
让他成名。
to make him famous
这就是它。
well that's history
是的，将军们也一样。
yeah generals too
更多的制造商。
they need more and manufacturers
他们富起来了，我觉得这更像是一种瘟疫。
they get rich I think it's more a kind of fever
没有人特别想要它。
nobody wants it in particular
然后突然间
and then all at once
这就是它，我们不想要。
here it is we didn't want it
英语人不想要它。
the English didn't want it
我们现在正在打仗。
and here we are fighting
我告诉你应该怎么做。
I'll tell you how it should all be done
每次有大战即将来临时。
whenever there's a big war coming on
你应该围起一片大草地，售卖门票。
you should rope off a big field and sell tickets
是的，而且
yeah and
而我就是那个大日。
and on the big day
你应该带走所有的国王和他们的内阁。
you should take all the Kings and their cabinets
以及他们的将军们。
and their generals
把他们放在中间，穿着内裤。
put'em in the center dressed in their underpants
让他们在球场上打架，胜者为最佳国家。
and let'em fight it out with clubs the best country win
现在猫已经解决了一切。
well now that cat settled everything
让我们去看看卡梅隆，路上可能会发生什么。
let's go see Camry something might happen on the way
男孩
boys
我和凯瑟尔
me and the Kaiser
明天要你回来参加游行，别忘了。
want you back in time to march tomorrow don't forget
他在那儿。
there he is
你好，卡米尔。
hello Camrick
你好吗？一切都好吗？
how are you how's it going
事情进展如何？他们对你照顾得好吗？
how are things going are they looking after you alright
他们对你如何？
how are they treating you fine
好的。
alright
这里有抢劫犯。
there are robbers here
劫匪
robbers
他们偷了我的手表。
they stole my watch
我一直告诉你。
I always told you
没人应该戴那么好的手表。
nobody should carry as good a watch as that
他们也在我被抓的时候拿走了它。
they took it while I was under arrest too
法国，你会得到它的。
France you'll get it back
你感觉好吗？
you feel alright
看看我的手吧。
just look at my hand though
那是因为你流失了太多血。
that's because you lost so much blood
只需吃点东西，你就会恢复健康。
just eat decently and you'll get well again
弗兰兹，你得吃点东西。
Franz you must eat
这是最重要的，看起来也很好。
that's the main thing that looks good too
我的脚痛得很厉害。
I have such a terrible pain my foot
我的右脚所有的脚趾都痛。
every toe on my right foot hurts
但你的脚怎么会痛，你的腿已经被切了吗？
but how can your foot hurt when your legs been
哦，我明白你的意思。
oh I don't know what you mean
我不知道。
I don't know
我切断了我的腿。
I've cut my leg off
他们为什么不告诉我？
why didn't they tell me
他们为什么不告诉我？他们告诉我吗？
why didn't they tell me why didn't they tell me
现在我再也走不动了。
now I can't walk anymore
你应该感谢自己只受了这样的伤。
you must be thankful that you come off with only that
我曾想成为一名森林管理员。
I wanted to be a forest stewardess
你可以。
you can
他们制作了许多美丽的假腿。
yet they make artificial lakes that are wonderful
你也完了。
and you're through too
你可以回家想一想。
you can go home think of that
我们为你带来了东西。
we brought your things for you
看。
see
把它们放在床下。
put them under the bed
这是一双绝佳的靴子。
that's a marvelous pair of boots
看那皮革。
look at that leather
我刚刚在想，这真是安慰。
what comfort I was just thinking
如果你不打算用这些，那么...
if you're not gonna be using these Franz
为什么不让我们带走呢？
why don't you leave them with us
对你有什么用呢？
what good are they to you
我可以用它们，我的靴子会让我脚上长疱疹。
I can use them my boots give me blister after blister
我们要去弗朗兹了。
we'll be going bronze oh
别走，多待一会儿。
don't go stay just a little while longer
我马上回来，很快就会回来，弗朗兹。
I'll come right back we'll be coming soon again Franz
我知道你会好起来的，儿子。
I know you'll be feeling better Franz bye
再见，弗朗兹。
bye Franz
你觉得自己有多脏？
you think you're allowed to leave the mess
你不认为已经完成了吗？
you don't think done for
你去了吗？
boys you go along
再见，拜拜。
I'll see you later goodbye
五点。
goodbye Paul
好的，保罗。
alright Paul
对不起，保罗。
I'm sorry Paul
我不会碰他的东西。
I wouldn't touch a thing of his
如果他能用上。
if he could use it
我为了他，宁愿赤足穿过刺丝。
I'd go barefoot over barbed wire for him
只为了他的好。
to do him any good only
只有为什么一些秩序的人会得到那些靴子？
only why should some orderly get those boots
我明白，妈妈。
I understand Molly
我们这里都一样，好的靴子很少。
we're all alike out here and good boots are scarce
请叫医生过来。
tell the doctor to come please
医生，隔壁的病人想见你。
doctor the man in the next bed would like to see you
先生，我已经尽力为他做了一切。
sir I've done everything I can for him
无济于人，那个小家伙。
there's no helping him poor little fellow
他说下次是弗兰。
he says next time Fran
你认为我会好起来吗？
you think I'll ever get well
当然。
of course
你真的这么认为吗？
do you really think so
当然，手术过后你就会好起来。
sure once you get over the operation
我不认为如此。
I don't think so
别胡说，等一下。
don't talk nonsense well
你会像新的一样。
you'll be as good as new
他能处理比这更糟糕的事情。
they fix up worse things than that
也许你会去康复中心。
perhaps you'll go to the convalescent home
靠近贝尔，其中一间是他的。
that's close to Berry among the Villas
你可以从窗户看出去。
and you can look out of the windows
穿过田野，望向远方的两棵树。
across the fields to the two trees on the horizon
现在是一年中最美的时节，玉米成熟了。
the loveliest time of the year now when the corn ripens
你可以不问任何人就出去。
you can go out without asking anyone
你甚至可以弹钢琴。
you can even play piano if you want to
哦。
oh
对不起，我不明白您的意思。请提供更多上下文或
oh but Franz
现在你必须努力睡着。
you must try to sleep now
哦，天啊。
oh god
这是弗朗兹·卡梅伦。
this is Franz Kermit
仅十九岁。
only 19 years old
他不想死。
he doesn't wanna die
请不要让他死。
please don't let him die
哦，是的。
well yes Franz
带我的靴子回家给我妈妈。
take my boots home for Muller
哦不，弗兰兹，不。
oh no Franz no
然后
and
如果我有我的手表。
if I have my watch
这是家啊，兰斯。
that is home Rams
医生
Doctor
医生，医生在哪？
Doctor where's the doctor
为什么没有医生在这？
why isn't there a doctor here
医生，快来！
doctor come quick folks
看上去就像你快要死了。
Kevin like he's dying
哪一条是被截肢的腿？
which one was that amputated leg
我今天已经做了一 dozen 个腿。
I've amputated a dozen legs today
床位二十六，先生。
bed 26 sir
你看了吗？
oh you see to it
我在手术室工作。
I'm doing the operating room
自早上五点以来，一个手术接一个手术。
one operation after another since 5:00 this morning
今天有16人死亡，你的是第17个。
16 deaths today yours is a 17
他们可能会在这一夜里死去。
they'll probably be 20 by this morning
今天看起来不错，做得很好，是的。
and look at the good very good today yeah
这个家伙现在都在我身边。
this guy is all with me right now
嘿，我猜他一个人。
hey I bet he's solo
我明白了，猫。
I got it cat
听着，一个数列的和是
listen the sum of an arithmetic series is
s等于a加l乘以n除以2。
s equals A+L times n over 2
有趣吧？
interesting isn't it
你想学那些东西干什么？
what do you want to learn that stuff for
有一天你会阻止一颗子弹，一切都会白费。
one day you'll stop a bullet and it'll all be wasted
我从中得到了很多乐趣。
I get a lot of fun out of it
简化中文： 我看到了他的身影。
Bos never used 51bce0c785ca2f68081bfa7d91973934 user
我的靴子。
my boots
我知道，你的生活。
my life
我看到他死去。
I saw him die
我以前没有体验过死亡的感觉。
I didn't know what it was like to die before
然后，我走出屋子，感觉到了。
and then and then I came outside and it felt
活着感觉真好。
it felt so good to be alive
我开始快速走了。
and I started in to walk fast
我开始想一些奇怪的事。
I began to think of the strangest things
像在田野里一样。
like being out in the fields
类似的事。
things like that
你知道吗？
you know
女孩们
girls
感觉就像有电在流淌。
and it felt as if there were something electric
从地面穿过我，跑向我。
running from the ground up through me
我开始了。
and I started
我开始跑得很快，并过了一些士兵。
and I began to run hard and I passed soldiers
我听到有人在呼唤他们。
I heard voices calling them
我跑了，我一直跑。
and I ran and I ran
我感觉自己无法吸入足够的空气。
and I felt as if I couldn't breathe enough air into me
现在我饿了。
and now I'm hungry
我现在不介意战争。
I don't mind the war now
穿这样的靴子去前线，真的很高兴。
be a pleasure to go to the front in boots like these
哈哈。
ha ha
这也是一个好发明。
it's a good invention just the same
破碎的各式各样的法则
to crack each separate laws
想想你所消耗的能量。
think of all the energy you use up watch
烧死哈哈。
burn to death hahaha
巡逻怎么这么糟糕？
how was patrol bad
一定很糟糕。
must have been terrible
他们有时间在收获时聚集。
if they had time to gather in the harvest
我们在樱桃树旁。
we passed the Cherry Tree
当他看到它时，他开始。
and when he saw it he started
他疯了，我几乎拉不走他。
went crazy I could hardly drag him away
美丽。
it was beautiful
我家有一棵大的樱桃树。
I have a big Orchard with cherry trees at home
满开的樱花。
and they're in full blossom
从高处看，像是一片单一的羊毛。
from the hayloft it looks like one single sheet
那么为什么？
so why
也许你很快就能请假。
perhaps you can get leave soon
你可能会被派回做农夫。
you may even be sent back as a farmer
一个女人不能独自经营农场。
a woman can't run a farm alone
这不好，你知道，无论她多么努力。
that's no good you know no matter how hard she works
收获又来了。
harvest coming on again
他在哪儿？
what's the matter with him
昨天他的妻子给他写了一封信。
got a letter yesterday from his wife
他想回到自己的农场。
he wants to get back to his farm
我们都想回家。
we'd all like to get back home
到了那个时候。
it comes to that
我想，如果突然间...
I wonder what we'd do if it were suddenly
又到和平时期，喝酒找女人。
peace time again get drunk and look for women
我会去寻找一个能穿上这件衣服的仙女。
I'd go looking for a Cinderella that could wear this
为了一个花园。
for a garden
当我找到她时，我将无视两周的时间。
and when I found her nobody'd see me for two weeks
我会回到沼泽地。
I'll go back to the peat fields
那些在啤酒花园度过的美好时光。
and those pleasant hours in the beer gardens
还有比拼接更糟的事情。
and there's worse things than cobbling too
看，我的家人。
look my family
我会给你一脚，因为你在说话。
I'm gonna give you a kick in the backside for talking
你们都可以说话，没关系。
all this it's alright for all you to talk
你有什么可回头的？
you've got something to go back to wives
孩子工作
children jobs
但我们呢？我们有什么要回学校的？
but what about us what have we got to go back to school
为什么不，你已经知道一切了。
why not you know everything already
一个人不能承受他们教给我们的所有废话。
a man can't take all that rubbish they teach us
真的，经过三年的炮弹和炸弹，
seriously after 3 years of shells and bombs
剥离它并不像脱掉袜子那样容易。
you can't peel that off as easily as a sock
他们从未真正教过我们有用的东西。
they never taught us anything really useful
像在风中点燃香烟一样。
like how to light a cigarette in the wind
或者从湿木中制作火焰。
or make a fire out of wet wood or
我不是个疯子。
damn that man
在腹部，而不是肋骨处，被夹住了。
in the belly instead of the ribs where it gets jammed
我们之后会发生什么？
what can happen to us afterwards
我告诉你，我们班的情况。
I'll tell you take our class
二十三中有三是办公室。
out of 23 are officers
九人死亡。
nine dead
穆勒和三人受伤。
Muller and three others wounded
一个在精神病院，我们都有一天会死。
and one in the madhouse we'll all be dead someday
那么就放弃吧。
so let's forget it
来吧，埃尔南多。
Haya Elena
快点。
Haya
怎么了？
what's up
军队中有公正。
there is justice in the army
嗯，嗯。
well well
所以我们都在这里，对吧？
so we are all here huh
比你稍微长一点，希米。
a bit longer than you himmy
自从什么时候开始，我们变得这么熟悉了？
and since when have we become so familiar
站在那里，合上你的手。
stand up there and click your heels together
滚出去，自己跳下去。
out of here take a run and jump it yourself
你的朋友是谁？
who is your friend
能有人给卢登多夫大将准备个舒适的椅子吗？
would somebody get General Ludendorff a nice
舒适的椅子哈哈。
comfortable chair hahaha
来吧，乔治。
like come on Josh
你的上司。
your superior officer
你想被警察抓住吗？
do you want to be caught by some police
我知道，今晚会有大规模的攻击。
I do there's gonna be a big attack tonight
我真的很喜欢脱离它。
and I just love to get out of it hahaha
你会听从我的命令吗？
will you will you obey my orders
你的脚我也爱
kiss my foot
哈哈
hahaha
这里不习惯要求敬礼。
it isn't customary to ask for salute here
我告诉你我们会做什么。
but I'll tell you what we'll do
我们要攻击。
we're going to attack
我们之前曾试图占领的一个小镇。
a town that we tried to take once before
许多人杀死了许多女人。
many killed many wounded
这次很有趣，你也来吧。
it was great fun this time you're going with us
我们中的任何人，在我们倒下之前，都能阻止一颗子弹。
if any of us stops a bullet before we die
我们要去找你。
we're going to come to you
合拢我们的脚跟，请。
click our heels together and ask stiffly please
sergeant Himmelstoss，我们可以走了吗？
sergeant Himmelstoss may we go
你会为此付出代价的，你。
you'll you'll pay for this you
哈哈
haha
这就是它。
here it is
准时到了，伙计们准备好了吗？
right on time better get ready boys
我移动了，我移动了。
I moved it I moved it
你这黄毛小子，刮了你！
that's a scratch you yellow rat up
快去跟其他人一起去吧。
get on with the others up help
你这黄猿。
you yellow rat
你是个小老鼠，让别人来做吧。
you think you're a rat let the others do it
起来，起来！
hey get up get up
啊啊
forward forward
好的。
come on
快点，前进，前进。
come on let's forward forward
前进。
forward
去吧。
啊
power
快点
如何攻击？
how to attack
我想帮你。
I wanna help you
我能忍受剩下的，我听不下去了。
I can bear the rest of it I can't listen to that
为什么这么慢，死去吧。
why do you take so long die
你终究会死的。
you're going to die anyway
不，不。
no no
等一下。
你不会死的。
you won't die no
不，你不会死。
no you won't die
它们只是小伤口。
they're only little wounds
你会回家的，一切都会好的。
you'll get home you'll be alright
你会比我早得多回家。
you'll get home long before I will
你知道我逃不掉。
you know I can't run away
这就是你指控我的原因。
that's why you accused me
我告诉你，我不想杀你。
I tell you I didn't want to kill you
我试图让你活下去。
I tried to keep you alive
如果你再跳进来。
if you jumped in here again
我不会这么做。
I wouldn't do it
你看，当你跳进来时。
you see when you jumped in here
你是我的敌人，我害怕你。
you were my enemy and I was afraid of you
但你只是一个和我一样的人，我杀了你。
but you're just a man like me and I killed you
原谅我，战友。
forgive me comrade
对我说，你原谅我。
say that for me say you forgive me
哦不，你死了。
oh no you're dead
你比我好得多。
only you're better off than I am
你已经过去了，现在不能再对你做任何事了。
you're through they can't do any more to you now
哦，天哪。
oh God
他们为什么要这样对我们？
why did they do this to us
我们只想活下去，你和我。
we only wanted to live you and I
为什么要让我们互相对立呢？
why should they send us out to fight each other
如果我们扔掉这些枪和制服。
if we threw away these rifles and these uniforms
你就像阿尔伯特一样，可以成为我的兄弟。
you could be my brother just like Captain Albert
你必须原谅我，战友。
you'll have to forgive me comrade
我会尽我所能。
I'll do all I can
我会写给你的父母，我会写给你的。
I'll write to your parents I'll write to
简化中文： 你好，我是来自美国的一名志愿者。
Bos never used 51bce0c785ca2f6808
我会写给你的妻子，我会写给她。
I'll write to your wife I'll write to her
我保证她不会缺什么。
I promise she'll not want for anything
我会帮助她，也会帮助你们的父母。
and I'll help her and your parents too
只求你原谅我，原谅我。
only forgive me forgive me
原谅我，原谅我。
forgive me forgive me
对不起。
forgive me
简化中文： 简化中文：
Bos never used 51bce0c785ca2f68081bfa7d91973934 user
昨天发生了一件可怕的事。
terrible thing happened yesterday
我用自己的手刺了一个人。
I stabbed a man with my own hands
刺了他，我知道这是怎么回事。
stabbed him I know how it is
第一次。
the first time
别担心，担架队会找到他的。
never mind the stretcher bearers will find him
哦，不。
oh no
他死了，猫。
he's dead cat
我看着他死去，你无法阻止。
I watched him die you couldn't do anything about it
我们都必须改变，无法避免。
we all have to kill we can't help it
这就是我们在这里的目的。
that's what we are here for
看，比如说。
look there for instance
那把他抓住了。
that got him
你应该看到他跳了起来。
you should have seen how he leaped in the air
那家伙今天是鞋匠的。
that fella heads the shoeblacks for the day
如果他继续这样，三次击中。
with three hits if he keeps it up
他今晚会有一个装饰物挂在他的领口上。
he'll have a decoration for his buttonhole this evening
别再为这事担心了。
why don't you lose any more sleep over this business
可能是因为我和他待在一起太久了吧。
maybe it was'cause I was out there with him so long huh
当然，就是这样。
sure that's it
毕竟，战争就是战争。
after all war is war
嘿。
hey
你好，你好。
hello hey
嘿。
hey
这是。
fuck this
啊
ah
呃
fuck this
哦。
oh
非军官，你的任务被取消了。
noncommissioned officers color a German dismissed
快走，我们离开这里吧。
come on let's get out of here
所有的火焰都把他们困住了。
all the fire that kept them
我为你的最好的部分而感到骄傲。
all this I brought to your best party thank you
一 二
1 2
三二一
3 4
嘿，走开！
hey get out of here
来吧，给我倒一杯啤酒。
come on get me a beer
一瓶啤酒。
a beer one beer
希望我们今晚能醉倒在地。
well here's hoping we get falling down drunk tonight
这是怎么开始的。
here's how it started
我忘了有这样的女孩，现在才发现。
I've forgotten there were girls like that there aren't
看看那些细小的鞋子。
just look at those thin little shoes
她在那双鞋子里无法走多远。
she couldn't march many miles in those
保罗，别谈论行军。
Paul don't speak about marching
你让这位年轻女士感到无聊。
you're boring the young lady
一千块。
thousand pounds
你觉得她几岁？
how old do you think she is
大约二十二岁。
oh about 22
不，不。
no no
那会让她比我们大，她是...
no that would make her older than us she's
十七
seventeen
那样的女孩。
a girl like that
让它好吧，艾尔伯特。
let it be good eh Albert
他在的话，我们的机会很小。
we wouldn't have much of a chance with him around
我们可以洗澡，洗衣服。
we could take a bath wash our clothes
好的。
all right
我甚至可能会去寻求法律的帮助。
I might even go so far as to get the laws
等等，等等。
wait a minute wait a minute
她现在离这里很远。
she's a long way from here now
看看日期，1917年5月。
look at the date May 1917
四个月前，是的。
four months ago that's true
好吧，无论如何，祝她好运。
well here's to her anyway
祝他们一切顺利。
here's to'em all everywhere
阿尔伯特
Albert
洗澡也没关系。
you might as well wash up anyway
好的。
alright
我个人更喜欢大一点的。
personally I like'em bigger around
这谈话到现在为止都在道德高地。
this conversation was on a high moral plane up to now
现在我们确实需要一个人。
now we do need a bath
为了什么洗澡？
a bath for what
你不会理解。
you wouldn't understand
这水太冷了。
this water is freezing
这浪漫的事情已经过了界限。
this romantic business has gone too far
但想象一下她美丽的眼睛。
ah but think of her beautiful eyes
哦 哦
oh oh
你的头发。
their hair
我们到了，不会错过任何事情。
here we are I'm not gonna miss a thing
走开，你在这里干什么，在做什么呢？
go away what are you doing here bathing
他们告诉我这个世界上有一些人。
they tell me there's some people in this world
每周洗一次澡。
takes a bath every week
女性
women
你想游泳吗？
Mensa you wanna swim
你真美。
vous êtes très jolie
小姐，请给我一个拥抱。
madame embrassez-moi
我下来了，你下来。
madame embrassez-moi madame suivez-moi
你，你。
madame madame you
谁是你的爱人，我要亲吻你。
qui t'a aimé embrassez-moi oh
你这是在干什么？
mais lui il s'en vient mieux que toi va donnez oh
你别这样，我自己来。
espèce D'andouille Mademoiselle
好的，我来试试。
Bonjour Madame
我想和你一起去游泳。
moi nager avec toi tu peux toujours Te noyer Hein
抱歉，我不明白您的请求。
oh baby
你真的很漂亮，小姐。
maintenant vous êtes très Jolie Mademoiselle
亲爱的，我正在刷牙。
kiss me I'm brushing moi
我要亲吻你，亲爱的。
moi t'embrasser et bien
你还可以继续在那边。
tu peux toujours courir derrière
马丁·本尼迪克特
Martin Benedict
哦妈妈。
oh Mama
我们就在这里。
we're right here
我们在前方。
we're right here we're right here
大家都在这里。
we're right here we're right here we're right here
嗯嗯。
whoo whoo
看这个。
regardez
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
mangez mangez Bon Bon whoo
别停，继续走。
franchement regarde j'ai faim
好的。
oh dieu
哦，我的天啊。
oh mon dieu
哦，我的天啊，你在哪儿？
oh mon dieu vous n'avez ici venez
你知道你不能穿越。
you know you're forbidden to cross
你们留在这一边。
you fellas stay on this side
你会惹上大麻烦。
or you'll get yourselves in a lot of trouble
你在哪儿？ 是的，我在这里。
vous habitez où ici monsieur pépé oui
你在哪儿？我在这儿。
je demeurez où ici pépé éteins-toi
我需要这块地。
vous venez tout de suite
他们在说什么呢？
what are they jabbering about
他们要我们今晚游泳过去。
they want us to swim over tonight
他们在等我们，没问题。
they're expecting us that's fine
我们就这么做吧，她对我疯狂。
we'll do it that blonde's crazy about me
我们有四人，他们只有三人。
but there's four of us and only three of them
我是阻止他的人。
I was the one that stopped him
那金发的小家伙是我的。
that blonde piece of work is mine
你三人争夺剩下的东西。
you three fight for what's left
战斗这个词。
fight's the word
爱和战争中的一切都是公平的，对吧？
all's fair in love and war huh
你是什么意思，你要怎么做？你会发现的。
what do you mean what are you gonna do you'll find out
战争中的一切
all of war
我回来了。
wait I'm back
简体中文： 简化版： 翻译： 这是我，这是我，这是我，这是我，这是我。
Bos never used 51bce0c785ca2f68081bfa7d91973934 user
是的，我是波尼。
qui VA là c'est moi blondie
嘿，嘿，嘿。
Bon ami Bon ami
好战友，好战友。
Bon camarade Bon camarade
哦，我不确定，你是黑人吗？
oh un moment d'oublie La Porte
她指的是门。
j'ai mis La Porte
你看过这儿吗？
vous avez vu voir CE qui se passe ici hein
我不知道，我们有个小姐姐。
I don't know we got this thing
哦，我的天啊。
oh my God oh my God
哦我的天啊。
oh my God
哦，我的天啊。
哈哈哈
oh my God
不仅仅是谦虚，而且是帅气。
not only modest but dashing
完美的配件，可能是为我定制的。
a perfect fit it might have been made for me
在警官中，我们跟随了卓越的公司。
as officers go we're following distinguished company
哈哈
ha ha
新的洗衣机。
new one please
安德烈
Mangez
你的手机。
tout
这是一个很糟糕的地方。
le monde est sale oh putain
就这样吧，就这样吧。
ça VA être sale ça VA être sale
等一下，别这么快。
谢谢你，我得到了。
merci à toi toi
来看看，这真的很有意思。
c'est gentil quand-même de venir
这真的很有意思。
nous amener ça c'est gentil de votre part
小伙子，给我一点面包吧。
pauvre garçon encore un bout de pain
是的，你知道。
oui donne-moi
啊 啊 啊
encore puis un bout de pain
你是个女孩，我也一样，我们都很幸福。
la guerre et toi aussi grand malheur
哦，给我。
oui écoute donne-moi
我很饿。
encore j'ai faim depuis
我很久没吃东西了。
il y a longtemps que j'ai pas mangé et toi aussi
你要吃吗？
tu veux un bout oui
你知道吗？
donne-moi tout
我也能把这一切都给你。
je pourrais manger tout ça moi
一个人，他说，“我要给你留一点，留给明天。”
tout seul enfin faut en garder un peu pour demain
哦，是的。
oh demain
这是一个危险的陷阱。 我们无法确定。
c'est un piège on ne sait jamais
再喝点小酒吧。
have another little drink come on in
是你的生日还是我的？
is this your birthday or mine
你为什么
why you've
你已经给我买了两小时的饮料。
been buying me drink after drink for two hours
我试图理解的是为什么。
what I'm trying to figure out is why
你在问什么？
why
为什么？
哦哈哈。
oh ha ha
哦，是的。
oh it
就是这样。
it's just like
一个男孩告诉我，为了逗你开心一会儿。
a boy told me to amuse you for a little while
哦，好男孩。
oh nice boy
是的
yeah
yeah they
他们说你会理解的。
they said you'd understand
我被背叛了，对。
I've been with three yeah
你肯定有，拿它去。
you surely have take that for a minute
我会给你更多的。
I'll give you more
太吵了。
it's too loud
小男孩，小男孩，你好。
pauvre garçon pauvre petit GARçON darling quoi
你叫什么名字？我叫苏珊。
what's your name Je ne comprends pas
你说的名字？
name you say name
乔杰特，过来。
Georgette come here
哦，我的名字是苏珊。
oh Mon nom Suzanne
这是啊
Suzanne
你叫什么名字？哦，我明白了。
et toi quel est ton nom Paul
哦
Paul
苏珊，你知道吗？
Paul c'est un Joli nom Suzanne
我希望能告诉你什么。
I wish I could tell you something
我希望你能理解我。
I wish you could understand me
哦不不。
oh no
不，亲爱的。
no it's impossible darling
我再也不会见你，我知道。
I'll never see you again I know that
如果我知道你，我也不会认识你，然而
and I wouldn't even know you if I did and yet
我总是记得你。
I'll remember you always
你
do you
哦，你能知道这有多不同吗？
oh if you could only know how different this is
与我们士兵相遇的女性。
from the women that we soldiers meet
哦，不。
oh no
不，我们要把所有的东西都放下，然后走。
no IL faut tout oublier
这是一场 terrible 的游戏。
c'est cette guerre cette terrible guerre no
不，不。
no no
不是战争。
no not the war
你，就是我在说的。
you that's what I'm talking about
哦。
you
似乎所有的战争都消失了。
it seemed as though all war
泰森
terror
奇迹般地，我从中脱离了出来。
and grossness had fallen away from me like a miracle
像我从未相信过的东西。
like something I never believed
哦，还有什么？
oh oh what else
哦，好吧。
oh what else
打个电话。
call Paul
我们要去，保罗。
we're going Paul
看看，我们有一个新的棺材。
have a look nice new coffin for us
我得说
I must say
这是一个非常愉快的准备，对这次进攻来说。
that's a very cheerful preparation for this offensive
非常体贴。
very considerate
但我看不到足够长的给我们的战友乔丹。
but I don't see any long enough for our comrade Jordan
别误会，我不和你说话。
mind you I'm not speaking to you
叛徒们，但没有棺材能抓住我。
you traitors but no coffin's gonna get me
我应该说，不是心碎的。
I should say not heartbreaker
你会很感激的。
you'll be thankful
在那儿放一个防水薄膜。
if there's not a waterproof sheet around that
和萨莉，你的一部分。
and Sally of a carcass of yours
哦，我的侧面。
oh my side
哦
oh
我的儿子。
my side
阿尔伯特天主教医院
Catholic Hospital Albert
他们说你总是能吃到好的食物。
they say you always get good food
好的治疗。
good treatment
我们在那雨后的修护站很幸运。
we're lucky after that rainy dressing station
二十四小时在火车上。
and 24 hours on the train
我们应该有点运气。
we deserve to have some luck
哈哈
hahaha
我是哈马卡。
I'm hannahka
是的，那是我的名字。
yes that's my name
我脑袋上有个裂痕。
I got a crack in the head
他们给我颁发了证书。
and they gave me a certificate
声明约瑟夫·哈马克定期
stating that Joseph Hammaker is periodically
他的行为不负责任。
not responsible for his actions
自那以后
and ever since then
哈马卡度过了愉快的时光。
Hammacher has been having a grand time
希望你们没受伤得太严重。
I hope you boys are not too badly wounded
呵呵
he he
其他人都很快就死了。
the others die off so quickly
我们没有时间熟悉彼此。
we don't have time to get acquainted
你会很熟悉我们。
you'll get to know us very well
谢谢，你也一样。
thank you you too
对不起，亲爱的。
I'm sorry my dear
现在该走了。
it's time to go now
是的，姐姐。
yes sister
看。
watch
如果他们夺走他的衣服。
if they take his clothes away
你已经见过他的最后一面。
you've seen the last of him
看，他们把他带到了客厅。
see they're taking him to the dying room
当你准备好了的时候，就会有一个死亡的小屋。
dying room when you're ready to kick the bucket
他们让你离开，以便使用床铺。
they get you out of the way so they can use the bed
建筑物角落里。
in the corner of the building
旁边有个小房间，正对面是球场。
there's a little room right next to the morgue
哈哈，太方便了。
ha ha ha it's so convenient
这节省了很多麻烦。
it saves a lot of trouble but
假设他康复了。
suppose he gets well
我见过很多人去那间死亡室。
I've seen a lot of'em go in that dying room
但没有人会回来。
but nobody ever comes back
嗯。
I'm sorry
对不起，我不明白你在说什么。
我很抱歉，我是在打电话给你的。
I'm sorry
是你的铃声吗？
is that you ringing Paul
是的。
yes
发生了什么？我觉得我有出血。
something going wrong I think I have a hemorrhage
绷带全湿了。
the bandage is all wet
我一直按铃，但没人来。
I've been ringing forever and nobody comes
我觉得我在流血，护士。
I think I'm bleeding sister
带上一包洗涤剂和一个冰袋。
get me a sterile dressing and an ice pack
为什么没有人通知我？
why didn't someone call me
他一直在打电话。
he's been ringing then we
没人能走了，姐姐。
nobody can walk Sister
姐姐，这有什么问题吗？
Sister is it bad
不，不。
no no
我们会好的，我们及时处理了。
we'll be alright we've got it in time
怎么了？你在做什么？
what's the matter what are you doing
我们需要重新调整你的绷带。
we must rearrange your bandages
你带我去哪？是要我去绑伤口吗？
where are you taking me to the bandaging board
不，不。
no no
我不走，我留在这里。
I'm not going I'm staying here
现在现在。
no no
我不去用餐室。
I'm not going to the dining room
我们要去包扎墙。
but we're going to the bandaging room
你为什么要拿我的衣服？
why are you taking my clothes
你在骗我，但我会回来的。
you're lying to me but I'll come back
我不会死，我会回来。
I won't die I'll come back
我不会死，我不会去死，我会回来。
I won't die I'm not going to die I'll come back
这位名人，他怎么样？
sister Liberty how is he
可怜的小伙子，他们必须截肢。
poor boy they had to amputate his leg
哦
oh
哦，是的。
oh yeah
走了。
gone
去了
你好。
hello
欢迎回家，阿尔伯特。
welcome home Albert
你感觉如何，小伙子？
how do you feel kid
好的，但我感觉很痛。
alright but I've got such an awful pain
我的脚受伤了。
my foot hurts
我去了。
Hamika
他们砍了我的腿吗？当然不是。
did they cut my leg off of course not
你有几个？有两个。
how many did you have two
你还是有它们，一二。
you still got them 1 2
别装糊涂，哈密克。
don't play the fool Hamika
真诚告诉我，当然不是，你看起来很好。
tell me truthfully of course not and you look fine
看。
look
嘿
hey
我不会成为瘸子。
I won't be a cripple
我不会活下去，我告诉你。
I won't live I tell you
我会第一时间自杀，阿尔伯特。
be calm I'll kill myself the first chance I get Albert
我不会活下去。
I won't live yes
you will I won't live Albert
阿尔伯特
Albert
阿尔伯特回来了。
Albert I've come back
我告诉你我会回来的，看，大家。
I told you I'd come back look everybody
我回来了。
I've come back
我不打算去哪里。
Paul I don't know where I'm going
我在那边，哇，我太高兴了。
I'm over there Paul I'm so happy
我回来了，从死亡中复活了。
America has come back from the dead
这很不寻常，从未发生过。
it's most irregular it never happened before
阿尔伯特，我们快点好起来，早点回家。
Albert we must get well quickly so we can go home soon
现在一切都会好起来的。
Albert everything will be alright now
是的，一切都会好起来的。
yes everything will be alright now
保罗，保罗，保罗。
Paul Paul Paul
什么事，保罗？
what's the matter Paul
没什么。
nothing
哦
oh
给我一条手绢。
give me a hanky
妈妈，我来了。保罗，我来了。
mother here I am Paul here I am
母亲在哪？
mother dear
你受伤了吗？不，妈妈，我得到了假日。
are you wounded no mother I got leave
我躺在这里哭泣，而不是感到高兴。
here I lie and cry instead of being glad
埃尔娜，拿下黑莓罐头。
Erna get down the jar of blackberries
你还是喜欢的，对吧？
you still like them don't you
是的，妈妈。
yes mother
我很久没吃过了。
I haven't had any for a long time
我们几乎能猜到你会来。
we might almost have known you were coming
我正在做土豆饼，别让它们烧焦。
I'm making potato cakes don't let them burn
哦。
oh
坐下，和我一起。
sit down beside me
米尔·帕尔
my Paul
我的宝宝。
my baby
我差点忘了，妈妈。
I almost forgot mother
我给你带了一些小礼物。
I've got some little presents for you
看，妈妈。
look mother
面包、香肠和米饭。
bread sausage and rice
保罗，你饿了吗？
Paul you've been starving yourself
我最好去告诉爸爸。
haven't I better go and tell Father
保罗回家了，如果保罗能看着炉子上的东西。
Paul's home if Paul could watch the things on the stove
不，不，查德。
no no child
我要起床了，哦，保罗。
I'm getting up oh Paul
你现在是士兵，不是吗？
you're a soldier now aren't you
但我 somehow 好像不太认识你。
but somehow I don't seem to know you
我把这些脱下来，妈妈。
I'll take these off mother
我去帮你找一下，保罗。
I'll get your suit Paul
在衣柜里，你离开的地方。
it's in the wardrobe just where you left it
你真的在这里吗？
are you really here Paul
你不会。
you won't
你不会消失吧？
you won't disappear will you
不，我在这里。
no I'm here
你的东西都准备好了，保罗。
your things are ready for you Paul
记得你那次抓到的那只。
I remember when you caught that one
是的，你夺走了它，对吧？
yes and you took it away from me didn't you
我做了。
I did
你在后方。
you're behind the lines
但我们知道如何尊敬继续前行的士兵。
but we know how to honor the soldier who goes on
在血腥和死亡中。
in spite of blood and death
先生们，我儿子。
gentlemen myself
玫瑰
roses roses
很高兴认识你，年轻人。
I'm glad to know you young man
很高兴认识你。
I'm glad to know you
那里的情况如何？
and how are things out there
很糟糕。
terrible eh
我知道
terrible
但我们必须继续，毕竟你在做。
but we must carry on after all you do
在那里，自然得有可口食物。
at least get decent food out there naturally
这里更糟，实际上。
it's worse here naturally
但始终为士兵提供最好的。
but the best for our soldiers all the time
这就是我要的。
that's our motto
那是我被教导的时候。
the best for our soldiers
什么是最好的？
the best for our soldiers what
哈哈，你得好好教训一下那些法国人。
haha you must give the Frenchies a good licking haha
如果你们想回家的话。
and if you boys wanna come home
让我展示你需要做的事。
let me show you what you must do
要回家之前
before you can come home
给我们点手，伙计。
give us a hand there men
现在，这里有一条线。
now then there's the line
这里是圣文森特，它在一个V形的道路上运行。
it runs so in a v here is Saint Quentin
你可以自己看，现在你快要过去了。
you can see for yourself you're almost through now
好的，前进吧。
alright shove ahead out there
不要固执地跟随永恒的法国战争。
and don't stick to that everlasting French warfare
打破约翰尼。
smash through the Johnnies
然后，当你进入时，你将得到和平。
and then you will have peace when you get in it
战争与此处所看到的不太一样。
the war isn't the way it looks back here
你对此一无所知。
you don't know anything about it
当然，你应该吃它。
of course you know about the details
但这与整体有关。
but this relates to the whole
当然，你无法评判。
and you can't judge that of course
你履行职责，冒着生命危险。
you do your duty and you risk your life
但你为此获得了最高的荣誉。
but for that you receive the highest honor
我说每名士兵都有铁十字勋章。
I said that every man of the motor has the Iron Cross
好的。
first
敌人的阵线必须在巴黎被打破。
the enemy lines must be broken through in on the Paris
在巴黎上演了。
push on the Paris right no
不，不，不是佛兰德斯。
no not in Flanders
现在我告诉你应该在哪儿打破。
now I tell you just where the break should come
敌人那里有太多的备用力量。
the enemy there has too many reserves there
我坚持认为是佛兰德。我知道。
I insist upon Flanders I know
我的亲爱的，为什么要这样做呢？
but my dear man why should they do that
当他们已经在圣文森特的中途时。
when they're halfway through Saint Quentin already
为什么走反方向？因为弗兰德斯是平坦的。
why go the other way because Flanders is a flat country
没有山，没有阻碍。
there are no mountains no obstructions
但那里有太多河流了。
but there are too many rivers there they
他们从农场离去了。
from the farms they have gone
从学校，从工厂。
from the schools from the factories
他们勇敢地、英勇地离开了。
they have gone bravely nobly
永不后退，意识到现在没有其他责任。
ever forward realizing that there is no other duty now
但要拯救无父子。
but to save the fatherless
哦
oh
你好吗，朋友？
how are you Paul
很高兴见到您，教授。
Glad to see you professor
你来的正好。
you come at the right moment
恰好在合适的时候。
Palmer just at the right moment
就像我所说的一切都得到了证明。
and as if to prove all I have said
这是第一个去的人。
here is one of the first to go
在这些椅子前，有一位曾坐在我前面的男子。
a lad who sat before me on these very benches
在战争的第一年，他放弃了一切去服役。
who gave up all to serve in the first year of the war
德国的铁血青年之一。
one of the iron youth who have made Germany
在战场上不可战胜的，看看他。
invincible in the field look at him
坚固、金黄、明亮。
sturdy and bronzed and clear eyed
你们每一个人都应该羨慕的士兵。
the kind of soldier every one of you should envy
哦，小伙子。
oh lad
你必须和他们谈话。
you must speak to them
你必须告诉他们什么是为父亲效力的意义。
you must tell them what it means to serve your father
你好，这是我第一次翻译，请多指教。
lad
不，不。
no no
我无法告诉他任何事。
I can't tell them anything
你必须去。
you must Paul
只言片语。
just a word
只需告诉他们他们在外地需要多少。
just tell them how much they're needed out there
告诉他们你为什么去了，对你意味着什么。
tell them why you went what it meant to you
我无法说任何话。
I can't say anything
如果你记得一些英勇的行为。
if you remember some deed of heroism
一些谦虚的触动，谈谈它。
some touch of humility tell about it
我不能告诉你你不知道的。
I can't tell you anything you don't know
我们在外边的战壕里生活。
we live in the trenches out there
我们战斗。
we fight
我们尽量不被杀。
we try not to be killed
有时我们是。
sometimes we are
这就是全部。
that's all
不，不，保罗。
no no Paul
我曾在那里，我知道那是怎样的。
I've been there I know what it's like
但这并不是人们常思考的。
but that's not what one dwells on Paul
我听见你在这念着那老套的话。
I heard you in here reciting that same old stuff
制造更多的铁人，更多年轻的英雄。
making more Iron Men more young heroes
你还是认为它美丽吗？
you still think it's beautiful
为国而死，真是甜蜜。
and sweet to die for your country
不要。
don't you
我们曾以为你知道。
we used to think you knew
但第一波轰炸教导了我们更好的道理。
but first bombardment taught us better
为国而死是肮脏和痛苦的。
it's dirty and painful to die for your country
当涉及到为国捐躯时
when it comes to dying for your country
宁可不死。
it's better not to die at all
外界有数百万人为了自己的国家而死。
there are millions out there dying for their countries
那有什么用呢？
what good is it
哇，你让我告诉他们。
Paul you asked me to tell them
他们在外地需要多少？
how much they're needed out there
他告诉你去死。
he tells you go out and die
哦，但如果你原谅我。
oh but if you pardon me
说“去死”更容易。
it's easier to say go
去死比去做更容易。
out and die than it is to do it coward
说起来容易，实际看得见的时候更难。
and it's easier to say it than to watch it happen
不不。
no no
好的，好的。
bye bye
对不起，巴尔默。
I'm sorry Balmer
但我必须说，这样谈话没有意义。
but I must say no use talking like this
你不会明白我的意思。
you won't know what I mean
只不过，我们已经入伍很久了。
only it's been a long while since we enlisted
离开这间教室好久了。
out this classroom so long
我想
I thought
也许整个世界已经学到了。
maybe the whole world had Learned by this time
现在他们才开始送婴儿。
only now they're sending babies
他们不会坚持一星期。
and they won't last a week
我不应该来休假。
I shouldn't have come on leave
前方，你是活着还是死去。
up at the front you're alive or you're dead
这就是全部。
and that's all
你无法欺骗任何人太久。
and you can't fool anybody about that very long
在那里，我们知道自己已经完了。
and up there we know we're lost and done for
我们是否已经死了或还活着。
whether we're dead or alive
我们已经经历了三年。
three years we've had of it
四年。
four years
每天是一年，每夜是一世纪。
and every day a year and every night a century
我们的身体是土，思想是粘土。
and our bodies are earth and our thoughts are clay
我们与死亡同睡同食。
and we sleep and eat with death
我们完了，因为你不能那样生活。
and we're done for because you can't live that way
不要把任何东西留在你的内心。
and keep anything inside you
我不应该来这里休假。
I shouldn't have come on leave
我明天回去，还有四天。
I'll go back tomorrow I've got four days more
但我无法在这里忍受。
but I can't stand it here
我明天回去。
I'll go back tomorrow
对不起。
I'm sorry
妈妈，你在这里会感冒的。
mother you'll catch cold here
你要睡觉了。
you must go to sleep
你走后，会有足够的时间睡觉。
there'll be plenty of time to sleep when you're gone
明天你要走吗，保罗？
must you go tomorrow Paul
你必须去吗？是的，妈妈。命令改变了。
must you yes mother orders were changed
你很害怕吗？
are you very much afraid Paul
不，妈妈。
no mother
有件事我想跟你说，保罗。
there's something I want to say to you Paul
只需警惕外界的女性。
it's just be on your guard against the women out there
这里没有好的地方。
they're no good where we are
没有女人，妈妈。
there aren't any women mother
注意前门。
be very careful at the front door
是的，妈妈。
yes mother
我会，我每天都会为你祈祷。
I will I'll pray for you every day
如果你能找到工作。
and if you could get a job
那不是那么危险。
that's not quite so dangerous
是的，妈妈。
yes mother
我会试着进入厨房。
I'll try and get in the cook house
那很容易做，你就做吧。
that can easily be done you do it then
如果其他人说什么。
and if the others say anything
这不会让我担心，妈妈。
that won't worry me mother
现在你要去睡觉，快点好起来。
now you must go to bed and you must get well quickly
我回来之前。
before I come back
我放了两套内裤。
I put two sets of underwear
新的放在你的包里。
new ones in your pack
它们能让你感到温暖。
they'll keep you nice and warm
他们都很热。
they're all warm
这真的很贴心。
that's sweet of you
晚安。
good night
我的儿子
my son
晚安，妈妈。
good night mother
妈妈。
oh mother
妈妈，你还认为我是个孩子吗？
mother you still think I'm a child
为什么我不能靠在你的膝盖上哭呢？
why can't I put my head in your lap and cry
这是第二家公司吗？
is this the second company
是的。
yes sir
这就是我们全部吗？是的，先生。
is this all of it yes sir
我们原本有150人，但昨天只剩下这部分人。
we had 150 men but this is all that came back yesterday
但现在他们会给我们足够的资源，让我们再造150个。
but now they're gonna give us enough to make 150 again
你几岁？
how old are you
十六
sixteen
不，你。
no you
我找不到任何东西，只能吃可乐。
I couldn't find anything we'll have to eat the soda
我不吃，先让我饿着。这让我恶心。
not me I'll go hungry first it makes me sick
现在又要打一场真正的战争了，保罗。
now it's gonna be a real war again Paul
老帕尔，我在这儿。
how's old Paul here I am
你知道，第二家公司现在很难找到了。
you know the second company's getting hard to find
没人知道你在哪。
nobody seemed to know where you were
我高兴你找到了。
I'm glad you found it
我猜我不太明白这件事。
I guess I don't get much of this
之前有食物在沙子里。
there used to be some food in the sawdust
现在全是木屑，没开玩笑。
now it's all sawdust no joke either
吃点东西。
eat up inside
这和老的第二公司看起来很不一样。
this doesn't look much like the old 2nd company
所有的替补都这样。
the replacements are all like that
甚至还不具备背包的能力。
not even old enough to carry a pack
他们唯一会做的就是死。
all they know how to do is die
我猜有些老兵还在，保罗。
I guess some of the old timers are here yet Paul
他们正在试图发明东西来杀我。
they're trying to invent something to kill me right now
西斯在哪？
where's Westus
传令犬受伤了。
messenger dog was wounded
他去拿它。
he went out to get it
关于和解，保罗，是真的吗？
is it true about the armistice Paul
后方看不太像。
doesn't look that way back there
他们想让我们继续战斗吗？
you mean they want us to go on fighting
他们说他们疯了。
that's what they say they're crazy
德国很快就会空荡荡的。
Germany will be empty pretty soon
哪里是达特里？
where's where's datery
他 homesick 了。你还记得樱花吗？
he got homesick you remember about the cherry blossoms
我猜他从那件事上没能走出阴影。
I guess he never got over that
他有一天晚上开始了。
he started out one night
回家帮助妻子管理农场。
to go home and help his wife with the farm
他们把他带到了后方。
they got him behind the lines
我们从那以后就没听到他的消息。
and we never heard of him since
他只是想家。
he was just homesick
但他们可能看不到它的这种方式。
but probably they couldn't see it that way
猫在哪？他呢？
where's cat is he
哈哈。
ha ha ha
不是他，他还在。
not cat if he were out
战争就会结束，你还记得他常说的话吗？
the war would be over you remember what he always says
他们最后才会救他。
they're saving him for the last
他在哪？他在找食物。
where is he he's out looking for food
正在收集材料做汤。
trying to collect something to make soup with
哪条路？
which way
下路两英里那边，我后会有期。
down the road about 2 miles that way I'll see you later
嘿
Ho
嗨，保罗。
hello Paul
怎么了？
how's the sign well
现在好了，一切都好。
it's alright now it's fine
有没有好运？没有。
have any luck no
总部已经把这个国家扫过一遍。
the General Staff's been over this country with a Rake
哈哈。
ha ha
仅限于。
exit only
告诉我，保罗。
tell me Paul
在家好吗？有个愉快的假期，注意安全。
how is it at home have a good leave and spots
怎么了？
what's the matter
哦
oh
我在后方不再有用了，猫。
I'm no good for back there anymore cat
我们都不是，我们待在这太久了。
none of us are we've been in this too long
年轻人认为我是个懦夫。
the young man thought I was a coward
因为我告诉他的。
because I told him that
我们学到了，死亡比忠诚更强大。
we Learned that death is stronger than duty
一个国家
one's country
老者说，继续前进。
the old man said go on
向巴黎前进。
push on to Paris
我的父亲甚至希望我穿着制服出入。
my father even wanted me to wear my uniform around
哈哈。
hahaha
那里不再是家了。
it's not home back there anymore
我唯一能想的就是
all I could think of was
我想回去再见Kat一次。
I'd like to get back and see Kat again
你是我唯一剩下的，卡特。
you're all I've got left cat
我剩下的不多了。
I'm not much to have left
我想念你，保罗。
I missed you Paul
至少我们知道这里的一切。
at least we know what it's all about out here
这里没有谎言。
there are no lies here
向巴黎开进。
push on to Paris
你想看看对面有什么。
you ought to see what they've got on the other side
他们那边吃白面包。
they eat white bread over there
他们有成群的飞机，但只有一辆坦克。
they've got dozens of airplanes to all one
还有能越过任何障碍的坦克。
and tanks that'll go over anything
我们有什么呢？
what have we got there
枪支如此过时，甚至会误射我们的同胞。
guns so worn they drop shells on our own men
没有食物，没有弹药。
no food no ammunition
没有官员。
no officers
继续前行吧。
push on to Paris
那就是他们在那边的谈话方式。
so that's the way they talk back there
我想我们最好走了。
I guess we'd better be gone
我对我贫穷的母亲撒了谎。
and how I lied to my poor mother
我告诉她这里并不那么糟。
I told her that it wasn't so bad out here
因为我们总是有很多人在一起。
because there was always a lot of us together
现在我和你在一起。
now that I'm with you
我开始相信我告诉她的是真相。
I'm beginning to believe that I told her the truth
走。
go
又有一个错过了。
it's another one that missed us
来吧，走吧。
come on let's go
等一下，老式红车好像坏了。
wait a minute looks like the old red wagon's broke down
我想我不会再走了。
I guess I don't walk the rest of the way
那把你的猫弄到了吗？哦，我觉得我把我的腿打破了。
did that get your cat oh I think it broke my shin
那也不太糟。
well that's not so bad
好的，我知道。
we'll get her
真是我的运气。
just my luck huh
好运，这意味着战争结束了。
good luck that means the war is over
哦，不，先生。
oh no sir
这个战争不会真正地打到我。
this war don't end till they really get me
这篇。
this one
现在放松，放松。
easy now easy
简单。
easy
来吧，我带你进去。给我你的手。
come on I'll take you in give me your hand
轻松。
easy
好的。
alright
好吧，小伙子。
well kid
现在我们要分开。
now we're gonna be separated
也许我们以后能一起做点事。
maybe we can do something together later on
战争结束时，是的，孩子。
when the war is over yes kid
你告诉我你的地址，我告诉你我的。
you give me your address I'll give you mine
一天不能带走我们两个。
you can't get both of us in one day
我们一定会再见的，猫。
ah we'll surely see each other again cat
记得那天。
remember that day
当你把整只猪带到工厂时。
when you brought the whole pig into the factory
在森林里的那一天。
and that day in the woods
当你教我们躲避炮弹时。
when you taught us how to dodge shells
我的第一次轰炸。
my first bombardment
我哭了。
how I cried
当时我还是个新兵。
I was a young recruit then
真的吗？
here we are
我们到了。
好的，现在是你的时候。
alright now cat
你会节省自己的麻烦。
you're gonna spare yourself the trouble
他死了，哦不。
he's dead oh no
他只是晕了过去，撞到了大腿，他已经死了。
he just fainted he was hitting the shin he's dead
你想拿他的工资簿吗？
would you like to take his pay book
你和他不相干吧？
you're not related are you
不，我们不相干。
no we're not related
你的事。
your deal
取他的名字和号码。
get his name and number yeah
斯坦斯拉夫·奇尼斯基三世
Corporal Stanislaw Czinski 3
0 6